Guide to the Papers of Abby Weed Grey 1922-1978 MC.151
New York University Archives
- Series V: Artist Files, 58033
  - Subseries C: India, 58063
    - Prakash, Om, undated; 58076 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Rama Rao, S.U., 1969; 58075 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Reddy, Krishna, 1966; 58074 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Sabavala, Jehangir, 1966; 58073 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Sagara, Piraji, 1965; 58072 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Samant, Mohan, 1966, 1969; 58071 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Santosh, Gumal Rasool, 1962, 1965; 58070 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Shah, Haku, 1967; 58069 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Sihare, Laxmi Pradas, 1968; 58068 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Souza, F.N., 1972; 58067 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Swaminathan, J., 1965; 58066 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Vivasvan, undated; 58065 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Vazifdar, J.P., undated; 58064 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Subseries D: Iran, 58044
    Contains pamphlets, published materials, correspondence, and biographical information on specific Iranian artists. Arranged alphabetically by artist.
    - Armanjani, Siah, 1966-1971; 58062 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Diba, Kamran, 1967; 58061 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Fizian, Aziz, undated; 58060 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Ghandriz, Mansour, 1966; 58059 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Grigorian, Marco, 1963-1964; 58058 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Khamenei, Hossein Musavi, undated; 58057 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Nami, Ghoiamhose In, 1971; 58056 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Ovissi, Nasser, 1975; 58055 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Pilaram, Faramarz, 1967; 58054 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Sakarians, Sarkis, 1971; 58053 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Sassoon, Sirous, undated; 58052 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Sepehri, Sohrab, 1962-1963; 58051 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Shabazi, Shahrokh *See Box 27, Fldr 1, 1969; 58050 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Spooner, Senobar, 1969; 58049 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Tabatabai, Jazeh, 1961, 1964; 58048 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Vartanian, Hacob, undated; 58047 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Zarrine, 1970-1973; 58046 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Zenderoudi, Hossin, 1962, 1971; 58045 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Subseries E: Tunis, 58042
    Contains a general pamphlet on Tunisian artists.
    - General Pamphlet on Artists, 1961; 58043 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Subseries F: Turkey, 58034
    Contains pamphlets, published materials, correspondence and biographical information on specific Turkish artists. Arranged alphabetically by artist.
    - Basaran, Filiz, undated; 58041 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Boronai, Aliye Berger, 1965; 58040 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - etinkaya, Orhan, undated; 58039 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Eybolu, Bedri Rahmi, undated; 58038 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Gursoy, Ahmet, 1968, 1970; 58037 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Kilic, Asuman, undated; 58036 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Marini, Aida, 1962; 58035 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Uluer, Rami, 1961; 162370 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Series VI: Index Cards, 1947-1978, 58022
  Contains notes and ideas on poetry, articles, poems, journal entries, and quotations. They are arranged chronologically.
  - Index Cards, 1947 January-1947 August; 58032 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Index Cards, 1948 December-1949 October; 58031 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Index Cards, 1953 September-1954 January; 58030 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Index Cards, 1956 January-1956 December; 58029 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Index Cards, 1957 January-1957 November; 58028 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Index Cards, 1958; 58027 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Index Cards, 1959 January-1959 December; 58026 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Index Cards, 1960 January-February, 1961 February; 58025 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Index Cards, 1963 May-December; 58024 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Index Cards, 1976-1978; 58023 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Series VII: Misc. Activities and Memorabilia, 1959-1975, 58001
  Contains interview transcripts, course notes, questions, speeches, lectures, notes, drafts, published materials, calendars, notes, correspondence, invoices, biographical information on Mrs. Grey, personal cards, clippings, and drawings.
  - Taped interview with self (Sets 1-54), 1960-1962; 58021 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Taped interview with self (Sets 1-54) - Edited, 1960-1962; 58020 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Course on Contemporary Art Questions (Index cards), 1959; 58019 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Lecture to Women's Club-Draft, 1964; 58018 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Lecture: New Century Club- Draft & Notes, 1965; 58017 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - "A Study in Genealogy", 1953; 58016 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - "River Stories," Agnes Weed Stoddard Johnson, 1978; 58015 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Calendars, 1970-1971, 1974-1975; 58014 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Notes on film "Norma Milburn", 1971; 58013 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Abby Weed Grey Interview Transcript, 1964; 58012 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Notes on course "Iran in Black & White," by Sam Peterson, 1967; 58011 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Minneapolis Society of Fine Arts, misc., 1967, 1970; 58010 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Minneapolis Institute of Arts, 1970; 58009 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Clippings on "Shah & Iran", 1967; 58008 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Child's Drawing, undated; 58007 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Valentine from Peter, undated; 58006 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Abby Weed Grey Biography (up to 1971), undated; 58005 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Ellen Johnson Gallery of Modern Art, 1975; 58004 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1966, 1975; 58003 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Clippings & Publicity, 1960-1969; 58002 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Series VIII: Correspondence, 57964
  Contains personal and professional correspondence arranged alphabetically by author or subject. Materials consist of information regarding memberships, art, artists, contributions, family history, Vassar College, financial documents, invoices, telegrams, clippings, purchases, and Parviz Tanavoli.
  - Ahmad, Sayeed, 1969; 58000 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    3 1142 04225389 1
  - Bartlett ancestor, 1976; 57999 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Cogswell, Margaret, 1968-1970; 57998 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Cousin Eloise, 1969 January; 57997 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Damavand College (Iran), 1970, 1975; 57996 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Deqhani-Tafti, Hassan (Bishop)-Notecards from letters, 1964; 57995 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Deqhani-Tafti, Hassan (Bishop) - Letters, 1969; 57994 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Eren, Cemil, 1970-1979; 57993 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Ettinghausen, Richard (Parviz' rugs), 1972-1974; 57992 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Farmanfarmaian, Monir, 1975; 57991 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Films (including Corke films), 1968-1970; 57990 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Gebara, Raymond, 1975; 57989 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - General correspondence, 1980-1981; 216165 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - General correspondence, 1982; 216166 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Gregory, Jane (photog), 1965-1967; 57988 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Grey Foundation/Grey Museum, 1972 July-1973 May; 57987 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Khaghani, Jamshid, 1966; 57986 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Kilic, Altemur, 1966; 57985 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Liston, Glenn, 1968; 57984 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1968; 57983 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Milkovich, Michael, 1975; 57982 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1962 July-December; 57981 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1963 January-March; 57980 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1963 August-December; 57979 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1964 January-June; 57978 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1964 July-December; 57977 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Mitchell, Geraldine, undated; 57976 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Museum of Modern Art, 1970; 57975 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Poems (MacMillan Co, Publ.), 1945; 57974 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Poetry, 1946; 57973 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Seichrist, Ron *See Photo Collection, Box 4, Fldr 16, undated; 57972 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Sherman, Elisabeth, 1970; 57971 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Tehran Museum, 1977; 57970 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Textile Museum, 1974-1975; 57969 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Turkish Art Today, 1966-1967; 57968 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Weed, Emmy Lu, 1922; 57967 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Whorra, Raveesh, 1977; 57966 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Winkler, 1975; 57965 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Series IX: Tanavoli, Parviz, 57937
  Arranged alphabetically by subject. Personal and professional correspondence (most of correspondence is from P. Tanavoli, and has been recopied or typed out, also correspondence is to P. Tanavoli, and to and from his wife Janet), clippings, financial and personal records, catalogs, brochures regarding artist's work, and invoices.
  - Catalogs/Brochures *See Separation Box, Fldr. 3, 1957-1980; 57963 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Clippings, 1959-1971; 57962 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence (Janet Tanavoli), 1969; 57961 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence from Parviz (typed copy), 1961-1962; 57960 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence from Parviz (typed copy), 1963; 57959 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence from Parviz (typed copy), 1963; 57958 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence from Parviz (typed copy), 1964; 57957 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence from Parviz (typed copy), 1964-1965; 57956 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence from Parviz (typed copy), 1965-1966; 57955 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence from Parviz (typed copy), 1967-1968; 57954 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence from Parviz (typed copy), 1969-1971; 57953 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence from Parviz (typed copy), 1972-1973; 57952 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence from Parviz (typed copy), 1973-1975; 57951 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence from Parviz (typed copy), 1975 March-December; 57950 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence from Parviz (typed copy), 1975 September-1976 November; 57949 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence from Parviz (typed copy), 1977 January-1978 September; 57948 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence from Parviz (typed copy), 1977-1978; 57947 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence from Parviz (originals), 1978-1980; 57946 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence from Parviz (typed copy), 1978-1981; 57945 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence to Parviz, 1969-1970, 1976-1978; 57944 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Financial Records, undated; 57943 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Galloway, David (Re: book on Parviz), 1977; 57942 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Minneapolis School of Art, 1961; 57941 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Personal Records, undated; 57940 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - "Prophet, The", Sculpture, 1963; 57939 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Venice Biennale, 1966; 57938 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Series X: Grey Gallery and Study Center NYU, 1970-1977, 214463
  - Chelkowski, Peter (Origins of Gift: NYU), 1970-1973; 214464 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - NYU Proposal for Art Gallery & Study Center, 1973; 214465 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Initial Selections, 1973; 214467 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Contextual Placement of Gallery Notes, Undated; 214468 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - NYU "Woman of Achievement Award", 214469 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - NYU/Gallery: "Berkman Proposal", 1974; 214471 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Gallery catalog draft, 1974; 214472 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Gallery correspondence, 1974-1975; 214473 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - "My Search for the Unknown Artist...", 1975; 214474 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - "Lion Rug" Exhibit, 1975; 214475 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - NY Trips - notes, 1975-1977; 214476 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Legal Correspondence, 1977; 214478 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Press Releases, 1974-1975; 214480 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Floor Plans, 1974; 214481 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Inaugural Exhibition: Artist List, 1975; 214482 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Inaugural Invitation, 1976; 214483 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, 1974-1975; 214484 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous, undated; 214485 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Series XI: The University of Minnesota, 57909
  All materials are in regards to the 1973 proposal of establishing the Grey museum at the University of Minnesota. These materials include professional and personal correspondence, architectural plans, and meeting minutes of the Grey Foundation.
  - Correspondence on Grey Museum, 1973; 57913 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    3 1142 04225390 9
  - Architectural Plans for Grey Museum, 1973; 57912 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Grey Foundation/University of Minnesota Negotiations, 1973; 57911 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Clippings, 1973; 57910 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Series XII: The Grey Foundation 1967-1969, 57899
  Materials are arranged in chronological order. Materials include personal and professional correspondence, clippings, film narrations, invitations, invoices, meeting minutes, and progress reports. The bulk are from 1967.
  - University of Utah: Benjamin Grey Memorial Lecture, 1957-1967; 57908 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Bronze Foundry at University of Tehran, 1964; 57907 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - National College of Arts Gift-Pakistan, 1966; 57906 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - University of Tehran Library Gift, 1967; 57905 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Gift: Exhibition of Student Sculptures, Tehran, 1967; 57904 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Foundry, 1st Student Exhibit, 1967; 57903 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Tanavoli Bronze to MOMA, 1967-1968; 57902 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Film: "Poet/Philosopher", 1968; 57901 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous minutes, reports, undated; 57900 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Series XIII: Grey Foundation Exhibits 1961-1972, 57859
  Materials in this series are arranged chronologically. Materials include professional and personal correspondence, invitations, clippings, catalogs (in English and other languages), scrapbooks (separated and located in Box 8), financial information, invoices, photographs (separated and located in Photo Collection), itineraries, reports, and notes.
  - M.A.P. Itinerary, 1961; 57898 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Communication Through Art, proposal, 1961; 57897 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Communication Through Art, correspondence, 1961-1962; 57896 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Communication Through Art, proposal, 1962; 57895 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Communication Through Art, proposal (edited), 1962; 57894 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Communication Through Art, correspondence re: proposal, 1962; 57893 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Communication Through Art, scrapbook *See Box 27, Fldr 2, 1961; 57892 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - 14 Contemporary Iranian Painters *See Box 27, Fldr 3, 1961-1963; 57891 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Communication Through Art, catalogs, 1963; 57890 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Communication Through Art, Report to USIS, 1964; 57889 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Turkish Art Today (Organization), 1964-1967; 57888 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Turkish Art Today (Organization), Western Association of Art Museums, 1961-1971; 57887 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Turkish Art Today (Organization), Publicity, 1966-1970; 57886 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Turkish Art Today (Organization), Working Papers, 1966-1967; 57885 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Turkish Art Today (Organization), Artist Info, 1960-1971; 57884 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Turkish Art Today (Organization), Customs & Bills, 1966-1967, 1971; 57883 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Communication Through Art, Turkish Art Today, Scrapbook *See Box 27, Fldr 4, 1966-1967; 57882 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Two Decades of American Painting, 1967; 57881 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - 1st Triennale, India, Correspondence, 1965-1967; 57880 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Contemporary Japanese Woodblock Prints, 1967-1971; 57879 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225392 5
  - Contemporary Art of India and Iran *See Box 27, Fldr 5, 1967; 57878 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Contemporary Art of India and Iran, Smithsonian Tour, 1968; 57877 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - 1st Triennale of World Art, India, 1968; 57876 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Communication Through Art, Indian Tour, 1968; 57875 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Communication Through Art, South India, 1969; 57874 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - "20 Prints", Minnesota State Arts Council, 1969; 57873 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - "Young Americans," Bogota, Colombia, 1969; 57872 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - SWANA Exhibit, SUNY Binghamton, 1969; 57871 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Communication Through Art, India, Book Presentation, 1970; 57870 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - 10 Young Artists, 1970; 57869 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Works Shipped (To or from Iran?), 1970 July; 57868 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Minneapolis College of Art & Design (MCAD) Exhibit, 1970; 57867 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Contemporary Turkish Painting, 1971; 57866 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Aquatennial Exhibit, 1972; 57865 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - One World Through Art, Minnesota State Fair *See Box 27, Fldrs 6-7; Box 28, Fldrs 1-2, 1972; 57864 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - One World Through Art, Minnesota State Fair (exhibit catalogues), 1972; 57863 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Exhibitions (catalogues): "An Exhibition of Coffee-House Paintings"; "2nd Triennale, India", 1967, 1971; 57862 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Exhibitions (catalogues): "Biennale Internazionale di Scultura"; "Modern Persian Painting", 1962, 1968; 57861 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Exhibitions (catalogues): "Moderne Iranische Kunst"; "Arte Turca Contemporanea"; "Art et Architecture", 1968, 1969; 57860 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Series XIV: Scrapbooks, 57847
  This series comprises multi-medium materials such as photographs, news clippings, clipped catalogs, and pen and pencil on paper notes.
  - Notes on St. Mark's Cathedral Church, John Dewey (From Box 3, Fldr. 2, Series II: Unpublished Works), 1941; 57858 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    3 1142 04225393 3
  - Shabazi, Shahrokh (From Box 14, Fldr. 8, Series V: Artist Files, Subseries IV: Iran), undated; 57857 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Communication Through Art (From Box 22, Fldr. 9, Series XIII: Grey Foundation Exhibits 1961-72), 1961-1972; 57856 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Contemporary Iranian Painters (From Box 22, Fldr. 10, Series XIII), 1961-1963; 57855 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Communication Through Art, Turkish Art Today (From Box 23, Fldr. 7, Series XIII), 1966-1967; 57854 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Contemporary Art of India and Iran (From Box 7, Fldr. 2, Series XIII), 1967; 57853 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - One World Through Art, Minnesota State Fair, India (From Box 25, Fldr. 6, Series XIII), 1972; 57852 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - One World Through Art, Minnesota State Fair, Iran (From Box 25, Fldr. 6, Series XIII), 1972; 57851 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - One World Through Art, Minnesota State Fair, Japan (From Box 25, Fldr. 6, Series XIII), 1972; 57850 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - One World Through Art, Minnesota State Fair, Turkey (From Box 25, Fldr. 6, Series XIII), 1972; 57849 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Tanavoli Exhibition, 1964; 57848 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Series XV: Oversized Materials, 57837
  - Travel Diary (1st) * From Box 9, Fldr. 10, 1960; 57846 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225394 1
  - Travel Diary (original & edited) * From Box 10, Fldr. 2, 1961; 57845 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Parviz Tanavoli Bronze Sculpture exhibition catalogue *From Box 18, Fldr. 10, 1976; 57840 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Ozzir Zuby exhibition catalogue, 1958; 57838 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Series XVI: Audiovisual Materials, 57720
  Access Restrictions
  Some audiovisual materials may be restricted. For more information, please contact the University Archives.
  This multimedia collection has been separated out into 4 boxes (3 paige boxes and one large archival box - approximately 5 feet of material). The collection consists of reel to reel tapes of 3", 5", 7", and larger sizes and cassette tapes. The reel to reel tapes of sizes 7" and smaller have been removed from their original non-archival boxes and re-housed in acid free boxes and sleeves. They have been labeled according to the information provided on their original boxes. In some instances more in-depth information regarding the content of the materials are included with the reels and tapes. No material has been separated.
  - Philip, Jean-Marc Masowsky, Shirley Goldfarb, Gregory Masowky, 1967 April; 57836; 1 sound tape reels (Box 30, Reel 1)
    3 1142 04225395 8
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
    1/4 inch open reel audio tape 1.5 mil acetate backing, 150 feet
  - Parviz Slides, 1967 July; 57835; 1 sound tape reels (Box 30, Reel 2, Box Access 13, Disk 42)
    1/4 inch open reel audio tape
  - Peg, Pierce, 1967 September 15; 57834; 1 sound tape reels (Box 30, Reel 3)
    3" reel 1.5 mil acetate backing, 150 feet
  - Poetry ? (one side only), undated; 57833; 1 sound tape reels (Box 30, Reel 4)
    3" reel 1.5 mil acetate, 150 ft.
  - Recorder, undated; 57832; 1 sound tape reels (Box 30, Reel 5)
  - Poetry for Ursula, undated; 57831; 1 sound tape reels (Box 30, Reel 6)
  - Peg 8/9/67, Brewster Hayes, Pres. Cole, 1967 July-August; 57830 (Box 30, Reel 7)
  - E.L.'s talk to century, undated; 57829 (Box 30, Reel 8)
  - 1.) Pierce, Peg telephone re: Allen Weller and AFA 2.)Cancel - (speech), undated; 57828 (Box 30, Reel 9)
    3" reel .65 mil tensilized polyester, 300 ft.
  - 1 of 3 reels taken from a 5" reel when needed an empty 12/13/67 - ? contents, 1967; 57827 (Box 30, Reel 10)
    3" reel
  - 2 of 3 reels taken from a 5" reel when needed an empty 12/13/67 - ? contents, 1967; 57826 (Box 30, Reel 11)
  - 3 of 3 reels taken from a 5" reel when needed an empty 12/13/67 - ? contents, 1967; 57825 (Box 30, Reel 12)
  - 1.) Peg C. '63-June 5? 2.) Pierce, 1963; 57824 (Box 30, Reel 13)
  - From Abby Weed Grey to Mrs. P.C. Weed, 477 Hudson St., NY, undated; 57823 (Box 30, Reel 14)
  - Unidentified, undated; 57822 (Box 30, Reel 15)
  - Unidentified, undated; 57821 (Box 30, Reel 16)
  - Unidentified, undated; 57820 (Box 30, Reel 17)
  - Torn Film- Parviz Tanavoli, 1969-1975; 57819 (Box 30, Reel 18, Box Digitized Access Files, File mc151_ref1303)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    16mm film, 50 ft, 1 min 30 sec, 24 fps, Color, Silent
  - Torn Film- Parviz Tanavoli 5" Reels, undated; 57818 (Box 30, Reel 19, Box Digitized Access Files, File mc151_ref1308)
    16mm film, 125 ft, 3 min 30 sec, 24 fps, Color, Silent
  - 1.) Clara & AWG--telephone fall 1962, 2.) Pierce, Paul Scheffler, August 1964, 1962, 1964 August; 176673 (Box 30, Reel 20)
  - Parviz Tanavoli, Sia, Barbara, 1964 May; MC151_ref1313; 57817 (Box 30, Reel 1, Box Access 13, Disk 43, Disk 44)
    3" reel.
  - 1.) Abby Weed Grey Poetry; Telephone-Parviz, Clara 1962 2.) Abby Weed Grey reads poetry; telephone-Max Lein, 1964, 1962; 57816 (Box 30, Folder 2, Box Access 14, Disk 12, Disk 13)
    3" reel 1.5 mil acetate, 600 ft.
  - Chuck Ario-recorder June 17, 1965 Recorder and vocal-Winter 1965 Abby Weed Grey and Lois Brigham re: Turkish Collection release, 2/11/66, also Bryskin India show Brewster Ghesilin 2/13/66 from airport Lois, Peg about 9/20/65 re need for arts festival in Iran Pierce Sia calls about Parviz' letter, 1965-1966; 57815 (Box 30, Folder 3, E-records nyuarchives_MC151, E-records ref1323)
    Format: 1/4" open reel audio, Size: 3" reel, Other: 1.5 mil. acetate, ft.
  - Abby Weed Grey-Turkey 1.) vacant, 2.) Turkey, consolidated, undated; 57814 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - 1.) Barbara Manning 2.) Jane Rubin 6/1/66 Hilly and Abby Weed Grey 6/6/66 re attorney and Walker Jim Haseltine (his voice) Letter to Paul Schettler (slip inside) Iran cable; Inez Quin, 1966; ref1333; 57813 (Box 30, Folder 5, E-records nyuarchives_MC151, E-records ref1333)
    Format: 1/4" open reel audio, Size: 3" reel, Other: 1.0 mil. acetate, 900 ft.
  - Empty Recorder Consort, undated; 57812 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    3" reel 1/2 mil. mylar, 1200 ft.